question_data = [
                     {"type": "boolean",
                      "difficulty": "easy",
                      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                      "question": "In the game 'Subnautica', a Spadefish will attack you.",
                      "correct_answer": "False",
                      "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                      "question": "In Super Mario Bros., the clouds and bushes have the same artwork and are just different colors.",
                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                      "question": "Sonic the Hedgehog; originally was going to have a time travel system.",
                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                      "question": "In Until Dawn, both characters Sam and Mike cannot be killed under any means until the final chapter of the game.",
                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                      "question": "The Mann Co. Store from Team Fortress 2 has the slogan 'We hire mercenaries and get in fights'.",
                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                      "question": "In Sonic the Hedgehog universe, Tails' real name is Miles Prower.",
                      "correct_answer": "True",
                      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                      "question": "The PlayStation was originally a joint project between Sega and Sony that was a Sega Genesis with a disc drive.",
                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                      "question": "In Space Station 13,  the station has a clown aboard it.",
                      "correct_answer": "True",
                      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                      "question": "In Resident Evil 4, the Chicago Typewriter has infinite ammo.",
                      "correct_answer": "True",
                      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                      "question": "Watch_Dogs 2 is a prequel.", "correct_answer": "False",
                      "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
